ASRI AZIZIYAH

+6289612080576 | asriaziziyah123@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Website | GitHub | Pekalongan, Indonesia (can relocate)

PROJECTS

Smart Solar Charge Controller and Smart Charger Dock for Electrical Scooter Monitoring System (HIBAH MBKM UNS 2022) – Monitoring Website

Dec 2022

Front End Developer and UI/UX Designer

Designed and developed user interface and user experience for the system, as well as coding and testing the monitoring website of the system using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP. https://baskara-mppt.com.

Workmotely - Project Management Website

Aug 2022

Website Developer

Designed and developed user interface and user experience for the system, as well as coding and testing the website using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, and PHP. https://asriaziziyah.github.io/workmotely/.

Portable PLTS Power Monitoring System (HIBAH MBKM UNS 2022) - Monitoring Website

Jun 2022

Front End Developer and UI/UX Designer

Designed and developed user interface and user experience for the system, as well as coding and testing the monitoring website of the system using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP. https://baskarasmartpv.com.

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro UNS - Organization Website

Feb 2022

Website Developer and Communication & Media Information Staff

Designed and developed user interface and user experience for the system, as well as coding and testing the website using wordpress and elementor. https://hmte.ft.uns.ac.id

Festival Ilmiah Mahasiswa SIM UNS - Event Website

Jan 2022

Website Developer and Head of Publication Design and Documentation

Designed and developed user interface and user experience for the system, as well as coding and testing the website using programming languages such as HTML and CSS. https://festivalilmiah.uns.ac.id

WORK EXPERIENCE

BANGKIT ACADEMY LED BY GOOGLE, TOKOPEDIA, GOJEK, & TRAVELOKA

Surakarta, ID

Machine Learning Cohort - Apprenticeship

Feb 2023 - Jul 2023

- One of the 5000 people selected among 67000+ registrants
- Learning and applying machine learning concepts, algorithms, and techniques to real projects.
- Collaborating with a diverse cohort of fellow students
- Gaining hands-on experience in data analysis, model development, and evaluation with TensorFlow
- Working on projects related to image classification, leveraging Python programming and data science skills
- One of the Top 68 Capstone Project selected among 787 projects with projects "EasyMeal"

ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING UNIVERSITAS SEBELAS MARET

Surakarta, ID

Basic Electronics Practicum Assistant - Student Activity

Aug 2022 – Dec 2022

- Assisting students in conducting experiments, learning about electrical circuits and understanding the results
- Providing guidance and instruction on the use of MATLAB and Proteus for circuit simulation and analysis.
- Setting up and maintaining equipment for laboratory experiments.
- Responsible for grading laboratory reports and exams, and providing feedback to students on their work

STARTUP CAMPUS Surakarta, ID

Data Science Student - Apprenticeship

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

- Collaborated with a team of fellow students at Startup Campus to complete a data analytics project.
- Contributed to all stages of the project, including data collection, data preprocessing, exploratory data analysis, modeling, and result interpretation.
- Utilized tools such as Python and SQL to analyze the project dataset, and visualize the analysis using libraries such as Matplotlib and Seaborn

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS SEBELAS MARET

Bachelor of Electrical Engineering

Bandung, ID Expected graduate 2024

Cumulative GPA: 3.71/4.0; Relevant Coursework: Information System, Data Structure and Algorithm, Basic Programming and Laboratory, Probability and

Relevant Coursework: Information System, Data Structure and Algorithm, Basic Programming and Laboratory, Probability and Statistics, Computer Organization and Architecture, Mobile App Development, Advanced Programming, Machine Learning;

SKILLS

Programming Languages: PHP, HTML, CSS, Python, Dart **Others**: Experience with MATLAB, Proteus, TensorFlow